Well, you know, they always talk about giving grace to everybody else.
You got to give grace to yourself.
One, humans are not infallible.
So there's that.
Like humans make mistakes.
Two, you are really, really, really formed by what you experience as a child.
And it takes a lot of time to not only come to that understanding, but then to have a
mature, developed enough mind to now synthesize that into growth.
And a lot of people don't do that at any point.
And they decide to take on those trauma traits as their personality traits.
That's why when you see so many people who are like, yeah, like I went through all of
this and like, that's, you know, that's what made me who I am.
And it's like, yeah, but that's unfortunate.
And oftentimes the way those things shape us is not always wholly into positive ways.
But then enlightenment is being able to say like, I don't have to take all of that.
That doesn't have to be my whole story.